vrcover.com 2019-06-02

# Privacy Policy - VR Cover

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

 **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, VR Cover collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use the website.

VR Cover also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. VR Cover only discloses logged in user  IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

 **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to VR Cover’s websites choose to interact with VR Cover in ways that require VR Cover to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that VR Cover gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, for purchases we require personal information such as your name, an address and phone number to make the delivery of goods possible. Those who wish to receive updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, VR Cover collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with VR Cover. VR Cover does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **Aggregated Statistics**

VR Cover may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, we may monitor the most popular pages on our site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. VR Cover may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, VR Cover does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

 **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

VR Cover discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on VR Cover’s behalf or to provide services available at VR Cover’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using VR Cover’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. VR Cover will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, VR Cover discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when VR Cover believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of VR Cover, third parties or the public at large. If you have signed up to the VR Cover newsletter and have supplied your email address, VR Cover may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new products, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on in the VR world. VR Cover takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

 **APIs  **

It’s necessary for us to use some “APIs” (Application Programming Interface) in order to process orders through the website, this includes processing payment and fulfilling an order. For payment you have a choice between:

 _2checkout  _– Whose privacy policy can be found here: https://www.2checkout.com/policies/privacy-policy

 _PayPal  _– Whose privacy policy can be found here: https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full

For orders of certain products to certain destinations we may also use a third party fulfilment service to ensure your package arrives as fast as possible. As such, some of your data must be shared with them to make this possible. We currently use the following:

 _EasyPost –  _Whose privacy policy can be found here https://www.easypost.com/privacy.html

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. VR Cover uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of the website, and their website access preferences. VR Cover visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using VR Cover’s website.

 **Business Transfers**

If VR Cover, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that VR Cover goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of VR Cover may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

 **Advertising and Analytics Services**

We engage third parties to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services about the performance of those advertisements. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of our Website and other websites, such as your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, date and time of each visitor request, referring site, browser type, language preference, links clicked and conversion information. The information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our website and other websites and better understand your online activity. We may also work with third parties to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign on other websites or platforms.

In addition, many web browsers support Do Not Track technology. Our systems do not respond to Do Not Track signals. Nonetheless, if you enable Do Not Track and it is recognized by our systems, VR Cover will not use information about your web viewing activities to tailor your online experience on the Website. Note, however, that our third party advertising providers may continue to use information about your web viewing activities to tailor advertising to your interests across different websites even when you have Do Not Track enabled in your browser. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [OPTOUT.NETWORKADVERTISING.ORG](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1) and [WWW.ABOUTADS.INFO/CONSUMERS](http://www.aboutads.info/CONSUMERS).

 **Your Choices**

We want to communicate with you in the ways that you want to hear from us. If you no longer want to receive marketing messages from us, you can contact us via the [contact form](https://vrcover.com/contact), or by clicking on the appropriate link at the bottom of our marketing emails. Please allow sufficient time for your preferences to be processed.

 **How to Access, Update and Remove Your Information**

VR Cover takes reasonable steps to keep your personal information accurate and complete. You can access, update and/or remove your personal information, including contact or account information, by contacting us via the [contact form.](https://vrcover.com/contact)

 **How We Secure Your Information**

Securing your information is important to VR Cover. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Website, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Website, and you do so at your own risk.

 **Privacy of Children Online**

We are committed to protecting children”s online privacy. In order to protect the privacy of children, VR Cover does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18 without prior parental consent. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child under the age of 18, we will delete such information from our records.

 **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, VR Cover may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in VR Cover’s sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [CONTACT US](https://vrcover.com/contact).
